{
    "subject": "resource/Graham_Leonard",
    "predicate": "ontology/predecessor",
    "object": "resource/George_Ingle",
    "human_readable": "Graham Leonard was preceded by George Ingle.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9343582987785339,
            "question": "Who preceded Graham Leonard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9215856194496155,
            "question": "Was Graham Leonard before or after George Ingle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7902145385742188,
            "question": "What is the relationship between George Ingle and Graham Leonard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6703625321388245,
            "question": "In what order did George Ingle and Graham Leonard hold office?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6309391856193542,
            "question": "What position did both Graham Leonard and George Ingle hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6072257161140442,
            "question": "Who was in the position before Graham Leonard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5539689064025879,
            "question": "Who was Graham Leonard's predecessor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.414633184671402,
            "question": "Who succeeded George Ingle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35924193263053894,
            "question": "If George Ingle came first, who followed him?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01904246397316456,
            "question": "Can you list the two individuals mentioned in the statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Graham Leonard was preceded by George Ingle.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4023_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If George Ingle came first, who followed him?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4023_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who succeeded George Ingle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4023_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Graham Leonard's predecessor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4023_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4023_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4023_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4023_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4023_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4023_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4023_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4023_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4023_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4023_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4023_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Graham Douglas Leonard KCVO (1921-2010) was a Bishop of London from 1981 to 1991, but do not provide any information about his predecessor. There is no mention of George Ingle being his predecessor."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about Graham Leonard being preceded by a bishop named George Ingle. There is no mention of another bishop preceding him in the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}